http://freedownloadscenter.com/privacy.html

Privacy policy
To execute the primary functions and provide the services intended, Free Downloads Center needs to collect some personal information about its clients.
You may, however, rest assured that Free Downloads Center respects your privacy and grants confidentiality for your personal data.
This privacy statement discloses the types of information we gather and how we use it.
Information collected
Free Downloads Center collects and stores only the data explicitly provided by the users while making use of the Services:
Information you provide directly to a Free Downloads Center Web Site.
Information about your computer and browsing activities on the Free Downloads Center Web Site, including through cookies and other technologies.
Use of the Information
Free Downloads Center uses information about its users only for the purpose of providing the services intended, including:
Provide the services you request.
Tell you about offers we think you will value.
Customize and provide the advertising you see.
Disclosure of Information
Please rest assured that Free Downloads Center does not provide the obtained information to third parties except co-branded partners,
and takes all reasonable measures to guarantee the safety and security of the user information.
Co-Branded Partners are reliable third parties with whom a Free Downloads Center Web Site may jointly offer a service or feature.
You will always be warned of accessing services offered by Co-Branded Partners.
However, consider that although Free Downloads Center does its best to protect your personal data, the company cannot pledge its absolute safety for the reason of not having control over information you chose to publicly disclose on the company's website (e.g. your comments and reviews).
That information can easily be seen, collected or used by any other unauthorized persons.
Third Party Sites
Free Downloads Center Site may contain links to third party Web Sites. Free Downloads Center is not responsible for the privacy practices of those sites.
How to contact us
If you have questions regarding the Privacy Policy, please
contact us,
and we will endeavor to respond to your request.
Free Downloads Center
© 2020 All rights reserved. Patent Pending.
